Guide to the Red Hot Organization Archive, 1989-2004 MSS.191
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XIX: General Red Hot Organization, 128614
  - Subseries A: Administration Files, 128615; American Express folders contain account information. Same for Checks, Cheque books, Deposits, Monthly accounting statements, Padell Nadell etc, Martin Greene Ravden folders, Bank statement folders, Information Document Request folders
    - Annual "closed books" reports and accounts, 1993-1995; cuid8112; 154030 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Arista Records, Inc., 1995-1997; cuid8113; 154265 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Bank reconciliations - Checking, 1994; cuid8114; 151998 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Bank reconciliations - Multiple, 1996 - 2000; cuid8115; 154108 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Bank reconciliations - Signature Bank, 2001; cuid8116; 154102 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Bank statements - Chemical Bank, 1994; cuid8117; 153937 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Bank statements - HSBC Bank, 2000; cuid8118; 157615 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Bank statements - HSBC Bank, 2001; cuid8119; 154107 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Bank statements and checks - Republic National Bank, 1996; cuid8120; 154068 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Bank statements - Republic National Bank, 1999; cuid8121; 157465 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Bank statements - Republic National Bank, 2000; cuid8122; 157616 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Bank statements - Signature Bank, 2001-2002; cuid8123; 154104 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - BCL Entertainment Corp. (Merchandising), 1993-1995; cuid8124; 153978 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Bills (Restricted), 2001; cuid8125; 155321 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Bills, paid: A--B, 1994; cuid8126; 152054 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Bills, paid: C, 1994; cuid8127; 152055 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Bills, paid: C, 1994; cuid8128; 152057 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Bills, paid: D--P, 1994; cuid8129; 152056 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Bills, paid: Q--Z, 1994; cuid8130; 152058 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Bills, paid (Box #2): A--B, 1994; cuid8131; 153944 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Bills, paid (Box #2): C, 1994; cuid8132; 153945 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Bills, paid (Box #2): D--G, 1994; cuid8133; 162254 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Bills, paid (Box #2): H--Z, 1994; cuid8134; 153946 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Bills, paid: A, 1996; cuid8135; 154079 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Bills, paid: A, 1996; cuid8136; 154080 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Bills, paid: C--D, 1996; cuid8137; 154081 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Bills, paid: E--F, 1996; cuid8138; 154082 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Bills, paid: G--N, 1996; cuid8139; 154083 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Bills, paid: P, 1996; cuid8140; 154084 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Bills, paid: Q--Z, 1996; cuid8141; 154085 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Bills, paid: A, 1999; cuid8142; 157638 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Bills, paid: B--N, 1999; cuid8143; 157639 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Bills, paid: O--W, 1999; cuid8144; 157640 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Bills, paid: A--C (Restricted), 2000; cuid8145; 157661 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Bills, paid: D--U (Restricted), 2000; cuid8146; 157662 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Blank forms, "List of Business Expenses", [n.d.]; cuid8147; 145319 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - BMG donation, 1995; cuid8148; 155301 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Budget, 2000; cuid8149; 154262 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Cash receipts and disbursements reports, 1996; cuid8150; 158384 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Cash receipts and disbursements reports, 1997; cuid8151; 158373 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Cash receipts and disbursements reports, 1998; cuid8152; 158362 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Cash receipts and disbursements reports, 1999-2001; cuid8153; 158354 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Cash receipts and disbursements reports; check transaction reports, 1996-1997; cuid8154; 154071 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Cash receipts and disbursements reports; check transaction reports, 1999-2000; cuid8155; 157480 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Cellular One Savings Book, 1994; cuid8156; 158065 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Checks, 1994-1995; cuid8157; 162126 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Checks, 1997-1998; cuid8158; 153874 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Chemical Bank, 1996; cuid8159; 158383 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Cheque books, Barclays Bank, 1991-1992; cuid8160; 151358 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Chrysalis Records / amfAR loan repayment, 1991-1995; cuid8161; 144569 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Clark, Larry film treatment, 1993; cuid8162; 147606 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence (Restricted), 1996-1999; cuid8163; 158055 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence - Miscellaneous (Restricted), 1996; cuid8164; 154132 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Davis Polk & Wardwell, 1995; cuid8165; 153894 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Dead Meat [Sue Coe], 1997; cuid8166; 157399 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Delaware corporation - Not-for-profit, 1994; cuid8167; 154074 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Deposit slips, 1994; cuid8168; 152015 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Deposit slips, 1996; cuid8169; 154070 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Deposit slips, 2000; cuid8170; 157622 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Deposit slips - HSBC Bank, 2001; cuid8171; 154145 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Deposit slips - Republic National Bank, 1999; cuid8172; 157474 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Deposit slips - Republic National Bank, 1999; cuid8173; 157476 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Deposit slips - Republic National Bank, 1999; cuid8174; 157477 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Deposit slips - Signature Bank, 2001-2002; cuid8175; 154146 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Detailed ledger by job, 1995-1996; cuid8176; 158382 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Dissolution of The Red Hot Organisation Limited (UK), 1995-1996; cuid8177; 144568 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - EasyPay tax reports (Restricted), 1999; cuid8178; 155310 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - ECD - paid bills, 1996; cuid8179; 157614 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Egan, Nick, 1991; cuid8180; 151343 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Exempt Organization Certifications, 1995-1997; cuid8181; 154110 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Expenses above and beyond, 1994-1995; cuid8182; 153904 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Expenses: Federal Express /Messengers, 1995; cuid8183; 153905 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Feinstein Management, 1996; cuid8184; 158069 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Finances, 1999; cuid8185; 154174 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Financial matters - Miscellaneous, 1993-1994; cuid8186; 154049 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Financial reports, 1995-1996; cuid8187; 158385 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Financial statement, 1996; cuid8188; 153963 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - First Institutional Securities, LLC, 1998-2001; cuid8189; 154109 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Fleet Bank - petty cash; statements, 1998-2000; cuid8190; 157620 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Form 990 - Grants, Allocations and Payments to Affiliates and Others, 2002; cuid8191; 155311 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - From Movieplay, [n.d.]; cuid8192; 160498 (Box 23, Folder 24)
      SyQuest 200 MB 5.25" Removable Cartridge
    - Funding/collaboration requests from HIV/AIDS service organizations, 1991-1992; cuid8193; 151346 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Funding application pack, Red Hot AIDS Charitable Trust, 1994; cuid8194; 151084 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - General Journal Transaction Edit List, November 1999; cuid8195; 157619 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - General Journal Transaction Edit List, 2002; cuid8196; 155303 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - General ledger, 1996; cuid8197; 158380 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - General ledger, 1997; cuid8198; 158372 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - General ledger, 1998; cuid8199; 158358 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - General ledger, 1999; cuid8200; 157617 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - General ledger, 1999; cuid8201; 157618 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - General ledger, 1999, 2001; cuid8202; 158353 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - General ledger, 2001-2002; cuid8203; 158070 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - General ledger, 2001-2002; cuid8204; 158071 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - General ledger, 2001-2002; cuid8205; 158072 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Giancarlo & Glieberman, 1990-1994; cuid8206; 154050 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Government Money Market Mutual Fund, 1996-2002; cuid8207; 154149 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Grants, 2001-2002; cuid8208; 154116 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Income, 1994-1997; cuid8209; 153890 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Information Document Request (IRS), 1997; cuid8210; 153942 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Information Document Request (IRS), 1997; cuid8211; 153943 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Information request, 1994; cuid8212; 151987 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Insurance, 1994-1999; cuid8213; 157621 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Insurance, 1994-1999; cuid8214; 157664 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Insurance, 2000-2001; cuid8215; 154115 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Intra-organization correspondence re: general accounts/cashflow, 1992; cuid8216; 147665 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Invitation list for Young Soul Rebels premiere, 1991; cuid8217; 151373 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Invoice approval requests/forms, 1991-1992; cuid8218; 151353 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Invoices, 2000; cuid8219; 154257 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Invoices: "Not Entered", 2000-2002; cuid8220; 154275 (Box 25, Folder 12)
      Contains invoices relating to Red Hot + Indigo and Red Hot + Riot.
    - Invoices: amfAR, 1996; cuid8221; 139297 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Invoices: Barclays Bank, [n.d.]; cuid8222; 145317 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Invoices: Cinram International Inc., 2002; cuid8223; 155314 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Invoices: Inter-company (Restricted), 1994; cuid8224; 153906 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Invoices: Martin Greene Ravden, 1992 - 1995; cuid8225; 144572 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Invoices: Paid, 1992; cuid8226; 151354 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Invoices: Red Hot & Movin', 1992; cuid8227; 147617 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - IRS - Correspondence, 1994-1995; cuid8228; 154051 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - IRS - Information for Application for Recognition of Exemption, 1993-1995; cuid8229; 154052 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - June 93 - June 94 account, 1994-1995; cuid8230; 145233 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Kaktus Valley, 1991-1992; cuid8231; 151132 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - King Cole Inc. - Entity information, 2002; cuid8232; 154277 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - King Cole Inc. - Incorporation, 1990-1991; cuid8233; 128616 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Landauer, Tracy (Balber Pickard Battistoni Maldonado & Van Der Tuin, PC), 2001-2002; cuid8234; 155308 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Lawyers Alliance for New York, 1993-2001; cuid8235; 154053 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Leases, 1990-1997; cuid8236; 153964 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Ledgers, 2000, 2002; cuid8237; 155312 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - License requests, 1991-2001; cuid8238; 154161 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - List of gay periodicals, [n.d.]; cuid8239; 162127 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Lounge $$$, 1998-2000; cuid8240; 157396 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Lounge - paid bills (Restricted), 1998; cuid8241; 157598 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Martin Greene Ravden - Company correspondence, 1992; cuid8242; 151355 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Martin Greene Ravden - UK correspondence, 1994; cuid8243; 153940 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Martin Greene Ravden - USA correspondence with UK re: 6/30/94, 1994-1995; cuid8244; 153941 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Memos, 1992; cuid8245; 151274 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Messengers, 1994-1995; cuid8246; 153908 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Minolta Business Systems, Inc. Maintenance Supply Agreements; CBS Whitcom Purchase Agreement, 1996-1997; cuid8247; 154133 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous literature, [n.d.]; cuid8248; 151752 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Money Market bank statements, 1996-2000; cuid8249; 158067 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      Includes deposit tickets, statements, transfer requests, grant awardees' information and more.
    - Monthly accounting statements, 1992-1993; cuid8250; 144571 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Monthly accounting statements, 1994-1996; cuid8251; 144570 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Morrissey "England's Answer to the H-Bomb", 1991; cuid8252; 151303 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - MTV, 1998 - 1999; cuid8253; 154173 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Native Tongues, 1991 - 1993; cuid8254; 151344 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Notes on operation of PAYE re: payments to casual and freelance staff in the Film Industry, 1990 - 1991; cuid8255; 147554 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Opening Entries Report, 1999; cuid8256; 157471 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Oppenheimer & Co., Inc., 1996-1999; cuid8257; 157663 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Organization cashflow, 1992; cuid8258; 147556 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Outlicensing, 1992 - 1999; cuid8259; 154163 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting), 1996; cuid8260; 153893 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting), 1996-1997; cuid8261; 153885 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting), 1996-1997; cuid8262; 153886 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting), 1997-1998; cuid8263; 153884 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting), June - Sep 1998; cuid8264; 153882 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting) (Restricted), Oct - Nov 1998; cuid8265; 153883 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting) (Restricted), Feb - June 1999; cuid8266; 153881 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting), Dec 1998 - Feb 1999; cuid8267; 153878 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting), Mar - May 1999; cuid8268; 153877 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting), June - Sep 1999; cuid8269; 153876 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting), Oct - Dec 1999; cuid8270; 153875 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting) (Restricted), 2000-2001; cuid8271; 153951 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting) (Restricted), 2002; cuid8272; 155316 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company - reports, 1998; cuid8273; 158386 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Payroll / Taxes (Restricted), 1995; cuid8274; 154072 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Payroll - Unofficial file, "Francine's" (Restricted), 1995; cuid8275; 154073 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Payroll (Restricted), 1998; cuid8276; 154087 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Payroll (Restricted), 1999-2001; cuid8277; 154089 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Permanent file, 1992-1994; cuid8278; 154118 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      Includes press packets, information on grants awarded, organization structures, legal forms.
    - PolyGram Holding, Inc. - Back end advance, 1998; cuid8279; 154264 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Posting reports - Republic National Bank/HSBC Bank, 2000; cuid8280; 158068 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Posting reports - Republic National Bank/HSBC Bank, 2001; cuid8281; 154147 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Posting reports - Signature Bank, 2001 - 2002; cuid8282; 154148 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Proposal (film), [n.d.]; cuid8283; 151135 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Ralph Lauren promotional CDs, 1997; cuid8284; 156558 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Receipts - Reimbursed (Restricted), 1993-1995; cuid8285; 153907 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Red Hot + Bothered / * Important Beat stills, 1994-1995; cuid8286; 160522 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      Content
      Apparently includes files on Beat Experience, America Is Dying Slowly and Red Hot + Bothered.
    - Red Hot #15, 1990-1996; cuid8287; 160519 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      Includes files on Red Hot + Blue, Red Hot + Dance, No Alternative, Red Hot + Country, Red Hot + Cool, Beat Experience.
    - Red Hot AIDS Charitable Trust/London office, 1993-1995; cuid8288; 145234 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Red Hot Disk 1, 1989-1996; cuid8289; 160496 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Red Hot Minis, 1990-1996; cuid8290; 160495 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Royalty statement - "We're All in This Together: A Benefit for AIDS", 1994; cuid8291; 154033 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Sebastian, Earle, [n.d.]; cuid8292; 151345 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Share certificate of John Carlin, 1994 - 1995; cuid8293; 145290 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Slogans, [n.d.]; cuid8294; 151372 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Statement of income and expenses, 1994; cuid8295; 158089 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Storage item list, 2006; cuid8296; 151740 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Strauss, Seymour (Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company), 1997 - 2003; cuid8297; 154276 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Summary of cash balances and related schedules of cash receipts and disbursements, 1994; cuid8298; 158117 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Summary of cash balances and related schedules of cash receipts and disbursements, 1995; cuid8299; 158118 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Summary of cash balances and related schedules of cash receipts and disbursements, 1996; cuid8300; 158119 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Tax audit 12/31/94 (Restricted), 1994 - 1997; cuid8301; 151988 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Tax audit 12/31/94 - "Our take" (Restricted), 1993 - 1995; cuid8302; 151910 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Tax forms (Restricted), 1990 - 1996; cuid8303; 151371 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Tax return filing instructions, prepared by Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Co., 1998; cuid8304; 154120 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Taxes - Foreign, 1996; cuid8305; 154117 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Trademarks, 1994-1999; cuid8306; 153957 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - UK Liquidation, 1995 - 1996; cuid8307; 153955 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - UK office: Correspondence, 1996; cuid8308; 153958 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Video tracking log: Misc., [n.d.]; cuid8309; 151693 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - W.A.D. Party '02, 2002; cuid8310; 158266 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Wire transfer requests/confirmations - Signature Bank (Restricted), 2001; cuid8311; 154159 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Women's Moves, [n.d.]; cuid8312; 151131 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Womyn for Womyn: a lesbian resource centre, [n.d.]; cuid8313; 128618 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - WTC Business Recovery Grant, 2002-2003; cuid8314; 155313 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Zoo TV, 1993; cuid8315; 147666 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material, 128617
    - Art Against AIDS - On The Road, c.a. 1989; cuid8316; 161600 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Envelopes - Downtown Arts Festival, [n.d.]; cuid8317; 161604 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Happy New Year from Red Hot Organization, c.a. 1994; cuid8318; 161599 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Information packet, c.a. 1993; cuid8319; 139233 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Invitations to "the heart of summer", [n.d.]; cuid8320; 161603 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Invitations to a party to honor The Red Hot Organization, 1995; cuid8321; 161429 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Postcards - Designs by David McDiarmid, commissioned by AIDS Council of NSW, (ACON) Australia, c.a. 1992; cuid8322; 161601 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Postcards - Levi's Presents: A Month of Music, [n.d.]; cuid8323; 161427 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Press clippings - The Condom Project, cuid8324; 162212 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Press clippings - General, 1993-1998; cuid8325; 139231 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Press clippings - General, 1994-2001; cuid8326; 162213 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Press clippings - Love in the 90's, 1995 - 1998; cuid8327; 139221 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Press clippings - Miscellaneous, 1991 - 1996; cuid8328; 151753 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Press clippings - Museums: New York, 1995-1996; cuid8329; 161606 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Press clippings - 10th Anniversary, 2000 - 2001; cuid8330; 139277 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Press clippings - Twentieth-Century Blues: The Songs of Noel Coward, 1998; cuid8331; 151912 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Press masters, [n.d.]; cuid8332; 139285 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Press master samples, c.a. 1998; cuid8333; 139247 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Press release - 10th Anniversary, cuid8334; 139282 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Red Hot Again Photography Auction catalogue, 1991; cuid8335; 154152 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Season's Greetings card, [n.d.]; cuid8336; 161430 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Stickers - Red Hot Organization, [n.d.]; cuid8337; 151832 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Stickers - True Love (in association with The Condom Project), cuid8338; 161602 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Subseries C: Photographic Material, 151745
    - Negatives: "[Suite] pictures Mark Valentine", [n.d.]; cuid8339; 151746 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise, 161293
    - All Access: The Horde Festival CD-ROM, 1996; cuid8341; 161407 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Red Hot & Skin; PonyCanyon Entertainment (Singapore), 1993; cuid8342; 161422 (Box 29, Folder 35)
      Double audio compact disc
    - We're All in This Together; GRP Records, 1993; cuid8343; 161421 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Subseries E: Awards, 160440
    - VH1 Honors, 1995; cuid8344; 160441 (Box 29, Folder 37)
- Oversize Series I: Red Hot + Blue, 1990; 105140
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material, 1990; 105141
    - Posters - Red Hot + Blue, [n.d.]; cuid8345; 131851 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Press clippings, 1990 - 1991; cuid8346; 153992 (Box [46])
    - Promotional single: "Night and Day," U2; Island Records Ltd., 1990; cuid8347; 160205 (Box 42)
      Sound Disc: Analog, 45 rpm; 12 in.
    - T-shirt order form, [n.d.]; cuid8348; 131864 (Box [46])
  - Subseries B: Red Hot + Dance, 169124
    - Red Hot + Dance - 2 inch Quad Master One, December 15, 1991; ID: 191.0155A; 172103 (Box 60, Media ID: 191.0155A)
      Format: 2 inch Quad
      TRT: Unknown
    - Red Hot + Dance - Master One - Recording Notes, 1991; cuid8349; 172104 (Box TBA, Folder ID: 191.0155B)
    - Red Hot + Dance - 2 inch Quad Master Two, December 15, 1991; ID: 191.0156A; 172105 (Box 60, Media ID: 191.0156A)
    - Red Hot + Dance - Master Two - Recording Notes, 1991; cuid8350; 172106 (Box TBA, Folder ID: 191.0156B)
    - Red Hot + Dance - 2 inch Quad Master Three, December 15, 1991; ID: 191.0157A; 172107 (Box 60, Media ID: 191.0157A)
    - Red Hot + Dance - Master Three - Recording Notes, 1991; cuid8351; 172108 (Box TBA, Folder ID: 191.0157B)
    - Urge Overkill - Take A Walk - 1/4 inch Open Reel, November 2, 1993; ID: 191.0158; 172109 (Box 60, Media ID: 191.0158)
      Format: 1/4 inch Open Reel
      TRT: [4 mins 36 secs]
    - Matthew Sweet - Super Deformed - 1/4 inch Open Reel, October 21, 1993; ID: 191.0159; 172110 (Box 60, Media ID: 191.0159)
      TRT: [3 mins 55 secs]
    - Urge Overkill - Take A Walk - 1/4 inch Open Reel, November 2, 1993; ID: 191.0160; 172111 (Box 60, Media ID: 191.0160)
    - Red Hot + Dance - Miscellaneous Paperwork, Folder One, [1991-1993]; cuid8352; 172112 (Box TBA, Folder data_value_missing_a2db954e4570bca2fac505d841807af9)
    - Red Hot + Dance - Miscellaneous Paperwork, Folder Two, [1991-1993]; cuid8353; 172113 (Box TBA, Folder data_value_missing_86e10f27e0dfb1c14057dd8d6b8867b4)
    - Red Hot + Dance - AIDS Dancathon - 2 inch Quad, Reel 1 of 5, November 30, 1991; ID: 191.0161; 172114 (Box 61, Media ID: 191.0161)
    - Red Hot + Dance - AIDS Dancathon - 2 inch Quad, Reel 2 of 5, November 30, 1991; ID: 191.0162; 172115 (Box 61, Media ID: 191.0162)
    - Red Hot + Dance - AIDS Dancathon - 2 inch Quad, Reel 3 of 5, November 30, 1991; ID: 191.0163; 172116 (Box 61, Media ID: 191.0163)
    - Red Hot + Dance - AIDS Dancathon - 2 inch Quad, Reel 4 of 5, November 30, 1991; ID: 191.0164; 172117 (Box 61, Media ID: 191.0164)
    - Red Hot + Dance - AIDS Dancathon - 2 inch Quad, Reel 5 of 5, November 30, 1991; ID: 191.0165; 172118 (Box 61, Media ID: 191.0165)
      - Red Hot + Dance 9PP4 - 1/4 inch Open Reel, 1 of 2, Unknown; ID: 191.0166; 172164 (Box 60, Media ID: 191.0166)
    - Red Hot + Dance 9PP4 - 1/4 inch Open Reel, 2 of 2, Unknown; ID: 191.0167; 172165 (Box 60, Media ID: 191.0167)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise, 131863
    - Limited edition picture disc: "Well, Did You Evah!" by Deborah Harry & Iggy Pop; Chrysalis Records Ltd., 1990; cuid8354; 160207 (Box 42)
      Sound Disc: Analog; 12 in.
    - Red Hot + Blue, 1990; cuid8355; 154016 (Box 42)
      Laser disc